瞧谁来了
Lookie here.
我今天太幸运了
My day is made. [Laughs]
我连早饭都还来不及吃 就要杀死我今天的第一个印第安人
I didn't even finish breakfast and I get to kill me a stinkin' Injun.
印第安人？
Injun?
你丫放屁 我才不是
Nah
我穿成这样是为了不会在大草原上被割掉头皮
I just dress like this so's I don't get scalped out on the prairie.
恩 衣服看起来是让人很信服
Oh, well, that's a convincing outfit.
也是 在外面那么多野蛮的人 很危险的
yeah u can't be too safe out there with savages running around
那么 你需要买什么
So, what can I do you for?
我要买5包面粉 一根上面加有花生酱的胡萝卜
Need some flour. Five sacks.And a carrot with peanut butter on it.
一共多少钱
what's that gonna run me?
一袋面粉45美分 那么5袋面粉就是...
Well, sack of flour's 45 cents. So, five sacks...
就是40...
is 40...
需要我重复一遍吗
Wanna get back to me on that?
恩 对了面粉在地下室 你可以自己去拿
Yeah, look... the flour's in the basement.You can fetch it yourself.
非常感谢
Much obliged.
哟 瞧瞧站着的这位美女
Well, lookie what we got here.
在红色大草原上独自站立的一朵金花
Sweet piece of red prairie meat out all by her lonesome.
-Nelly 你觉得如何 -我觉得这位美人在等你
- What do you make of that, Nelly?-Oh, I think she's waiting on you, Will.
我们来鸟
Here we go.
你肯定在想 像我们5个风流倜傥 有着完美下颚弧度的男淫
Now, you must be wondering why five badass hombres with perfect jawlines...
都喜欢像你一样的印第安妞
all spot the same stylish Apatch.
关我毛线事
Not my business.
我们几个都把眼睛挖出来了 这是我们帮派的象征
We all carved our eyeballs out our skull to show how devoted we are to this gang.
我们是左眼帮派
We the Left-Eye Boys!
美女 你的眼睛太漂亮了 你觉得我们可不可以...借一只？
You got real pretty eyes, miss.You reckon we can, I don't know, borrow one?
你们觉得问女士这种问题合适吗
Now, is that a proper question to ask a lady?
小子 你特么谁啊? 男盆友?
Who are you, slick? The boyfriend?
马上就是丈夫了
Soon to be the husband.
等一下 我看出来了 他是个白人!
Oh, wait a minute! That's a white boy under that getup.
操 是个白人！
That's a white boy? Oh, shit.
你这个黄脸白种人是不是电影《风中奇缘》看多了 喜欢印第安人装扮？
You partial to pale faces, Poca-hot-tits?
我让你见识一下真正的白人什么样
'Cause I can show you what a real white man's like.
对 Will 让他见识一下 跳起来 赶紧儿得 真有白人范儿
Yeah, show her, Will. Yeah, go on. Yeah, shuffle up, Will.
现在我倒真想把眼睛挖出来了
Now, I do want to carve my eyes out.
你特么说什么？ -同志们 注意了
- What'd you say? - Hey, fellers
在我还没有正式开始之前 我就会打到你们
I'd hit the trail before you get hurt.
你有没有搞错？ 你会打到我们？
Before we get hurt?
我觉得你是不是抽印第安人的烟斗抽多了 假印第安人
I think you've been smokin' too much of that peace pipe, kemo-slobby.
你不要忘了 我们有5个人 而你只有1个人
Now, from what I see, there's one of you,
现在只剩4个人了你们
Four of you
刚才发生了什么事情？
What just happened?
傻逼们 还想看一次吗？
You wanna see it again?
呃...宝宝想看
Uh... yes.
-宝宝觉得不好玩了- 别吭气 傻逼
I don't like this shit.- Shut up.
恩...你的佛山无影脚练的不错嘛
Well, that's some, uh...real fancy footwork.
但是觉得这场胡闹该用武器来结束了
But I think this hullabaloo has escalated to the firearms stage.
伙伴们 把枪上膛
Boys, let's ventilate this.
谁能告诉宝宝刚才发生什么事情了？|
What the shit that just happened?
动手之前 撂倒你们 就这么简单
"Hit the trail." It was so simple.
小白飞刀 你不能再这样做了 以后万一人多起来怎么办？
You must stop doing this, White Knife. One day, there will be too many.
今天肯定不会了 小狐狸
But not today, Smoking Fox.
拜托亲爱的 我们应该出发了
Please, my love... we must go.
外面都发生了什么事情！
What the hell happened out here?
来了一群印第安人 他们朝那个方向走了
Injuns. They went that way.
你他妈才不是白人 你是那个孤儿 小白飞刀 像个野兽一样的被印第安人带大
You ain't no white man. You're that orphan, White Knife. Raised like an animal with those Apaches.
你以为你骗得了那群人吗？
You think you can fool of them?
对不起了 我的小马孩子~
Aorry Ringo
现在我要开枪把你和你的印第安小婊砸打死
Well, now I'm gonna shoot you and your Injun whore.
借用一下你的早餐
Gotta cut breakfast short.
你这个贱人！
You suck, mister!
电影名-《傻逼6人帮》
小狐狸 你真幸运 小白飞刀是一个非常勇敢的男人
You lucky, Smoking Fox. White Knife all man. Bravest of all braves.
才不勇敢 傻乎乎的
Not brave. Foolish.
我才不想这么早当寡妇
I want to be wife, not widow
女士们 下午好啊
Afternoon, ladies.
这是我们印第安人的地盘
This is Apache land.
酋长 我不是来这里掠夺你们的土地的 我只是来找一个男人
I'm not here to take your land, Chief. I'm just looking for a particular boy.
我叫Frank Stockburn
I'm Frank Stockburn.
这个男人的母亲是我妻子
This boy's mother was my wife.
这个男人叫Tommy 他是我的儿子
And the boy, Tommy...he's my son.
有时候相信未必不是一件好事 小白飞刀 万事开端是需要你简单地向前跨出第一步
It is wise to be slow to trust, White Knife. But every new journey begins with a single step.
主动和你父亲谈谈吧
Speak with your father.
苍鹰 你才是我的父亲 在我母亲...之后 你找到并且抚养我成人
But you are my father, Screaming Eagle.Ever since my mother...Ever since you found me...
你教我如何打猎 如何斗争 何时该说话 何时保持沉默 如何做人
you taught me to hunt, to fight...when to speak and when to be silent.To be a man.
做一个好人
A good man.
这个自称我父亲的人 满嘴谎言  和其他白人没什么区别
And this Frank Stockburn,he is filled with lies, just like every other white man.
有时白人也说实话 但是只有千分之一的概率
Sometimes, the whiteman speaks the truth.Like, one in 20, 25 times.
我觉得这次就是那千分之一的概率
I believe this is one of those times.
他毕竟认识你的母亲 跟他谈谈吧 说不定能带给你内心的平静
He knew your mother, White Knife. Maybe he can give you some peace. Talk to him.
让我好好睡一觉再说吧
Maybe after I close my eyes to dream.
你都知道我做了很多坏事吧？
One look at me, and you knew your old man had done a lot of bad things, didn't ya?
我偷拐抢骗 杀人放火
I cheated men, I killed men...
所以我活该现在这样
So I deserve whatever's comin' to me.
曾经只有你母亲看到了我善良的一面
The only one that ever saw any good in me was your mother.
你到底来这做什么?
Why have you come here?
肯定不是过来给你闲聊的
Not a man for chitchat, huh? Well, me neither.
孩子 我快活不久了
Kid, I'm dying...of consumption.
不用担心 我不是过来和你叙旧的
Don't worry...I'm not looking for no big father-son hoo-ah.
"我爱你 儿子" "我也爱你 爸爸"
"I love you, son.""I love you too, Daddy."
肯定不可能像这样 我来这里是为了你
No I've come for a more tangible reason
Tommy 我从9岁就开始偷东西 到现在我已经积累了一笔不小的财富
Tommy, I've been stealing from folks since I was nine years old...and that's the way I've amassed a good little fortune.
我想在我死前做点正派的事情 我想把这笔钱留给你
I wanna do something decent with it.I want to give it to you, son.
我是不会要你的一分钱的
I don't want your money.
但是你可以把这笔...5万美元给抚养过你的善良的印第安人呀
But maybe you could give...$50,000 to these nice Injuns who raised you.
我们收下啦！
We'll take it.
快回你的帐篷里去
Go back to bed.
不好意思 但是我真的觉得我们应该收下
Sorry. Seriously, though, we'll take it.
听着 钱埋在 铁路旁边的草地上 一颗松树下 我们明早就去挖 怎样？
Look, it's buried in the meadow just up the trail,next to a big ol' pine tree.What do you say we go dig it up in the morning
顺便过下圣诞节？
and start playing Santa Claus?
虽然关于我母亲的事情我已经记不太清楚了...但是我很清楚记得她告诉过我...
I don't remember much about my mother...but I do remember her telling me...
你早就已经死了
you were dead.
可能是因为...她不想你来找我
Maybe it was because...she didn't want you to come looking for me.
她是一位聪明的女士 唯一做的蠢事就是爱上我
She was a smart lady.Only stupid thing she ever did was fall for me.
遇到你母亲 是我这辈子最幸运的事
Meeting Betty Dunson...was the luckiest thing that ever happened to me.
当时在银色峡谷 我第一眼看倒你母亲 她正在向一个喝醉酒的大块头铁匠大吼大叫
From the first day I laid eyes on her...she was bawlin' out this...half-drunk, big ol' burly blacksmith... down at Silver Canyon.
她是我今生的唯一
She's been the only one, Tommy.
我母亲原来脾气这么暴躁？
Mom had a temper?
糟糕？ 你妈发起火来 谁都要遭殃
Temper? When she got her dander up, look out.
有次我们在一个酒吧里 你妈旁边坐了个人 他开始说如何做一个完美的樱桃派...
We was in a saloon once.This fellow sitting next to her starts talking about the perfect way to make a cherry pie...
然后你妈跟我说 你到底从哪里找来的花送给他们的？
So your mom says to me, Frank, come here a minute.Tell me again, just where did you get them flowers?"
我回答说 我知道你认为我是从墓地里面偷来的 哈哈
I said, "I know that you think I stole them from the graveyard."
帅哥们 早上好
Good morning, boys.
早上好 从来不穿咪咪罩的美女
Morning, Never Wears Bra.
小白飞刀 昨天晚上我梦到你了
I had dream about you last night, White Knife.
恩 很好啊
Oh, that's nice.
可不怎么好哦 在梦里你很淘气 灰常灰常淘气哦
Not nice dream.In dream, you naughty. You naughty, white knife.
看起来 我儿子很受欢迎嘛
Mmm, somebody's got an admirer.
话虽如此 但是和你一样 我这一辈子只有一个女人
Yes, yes.But like you, there's only one woman for me.
我们一家人都是...
I guess we Stockburns are...
用情都很专一
partial to the sweet ones.
的确如此
Yes, sir.
就像我对你母亲一样
Like your mother.
她怎么死的?
How did she die, Tommy?
能告诉我吗
You tell me?
有一天 学校里的一群大孩子决定要揍我
Well, there were these big kids at school fixin' to beat me up.
我自己不敢面对 于是我让我她一起陪我过去
Instead of facing them myself,I had her walk me there.
突然冒出一个人 掏出手枪击中了我母亲
This feller comes out of nowhere...walks right up to her and shoots her dead.
她当场就死掉了 要不是保护我这个没用的儿子 她本应该在家里 毫发无损的
So that's how she died,protecting her gutless son instead of being home,safe where she belonged.
谁过来了？Bony Express？
Who's that? Is that Bony Express?
Bony Express怎么会找到这里
Bony Express on't come around here.
他就在这里 让我们把他熏出来
He's here somewhere, boys.Let's burn him out!
下一个目标就是你的额头
Next one goes through your forehead.
嘿嘿 不要动手！
Hey, hey! No need to burn nothing, boys!
好久不见 老大
Howdy, boss.
Cicero...我退休了 你也不放过我
Cicero...you're not gonna let a man enjoy his retirement, are ya?
Frank  当然不是 你金盆洗手 我当然没有意见 只不过那笔钱...
No, Frank, I salute your decision to turn from your sinful ways.But the money...
是我们共同的财产
that belongs to all of us.
小子 你只要动手 我枪子儿里的子弹可手下不留情
Touch that steel, boy,I got plenty of bullets left over after I put one in...
第一个遭殃的就是你父亲
your father.
噢 看来你已经找到了你失散多年儿子 我也不想打扰你们的全家团圆的
Oh, you finally found your long lost son. Well, I sure hate to break up this nice family reunion.
那为何你不干脆把钱交出来 不然你就等着吃子弹吧
So, why don't you give us the money you stole before I put lead in your head.
钱已经被埋起来了
The money's buried.
儿子 不要多说
Way to run your mouth, son.
被埋起来了？
It's buried?
对 我把钱深埋在地下 在一架风车旁边
Yeah, I buried it.Deep in the ground...next to a windmill.
一架风车旁边？我操 这范围也太特么大了
A windmill in the West...doesn't narrow it down much, Frank.
这架风车不一样...它会唱歌
Well, this is a special windmill.It's a singing windmill.
你他妈当我傻逼呢？
A singing windmill!
从这里出发要10天 我答应带你去找钱 只要你保证...
It's about a ten-day ride from here.I'll lead you to it presently on one condition.
不要伤害我的儿子 和其他这些善良的印第安人
You don't hurt my boy...or any of these kindly Injuns here.
走 我们现在就出发
Let's ride, Frank.
如果到时候风车下面没有挖到钱 我会把你活埋 只露出头 让沙漠上的动物活生生地吃了你
Frank, if that $50,000 isn't under that windmill,I'm gonna bury you up to your neck and let the desert critters eat you alive.
我保证钱在那里 我很高兴我找到了我的儿子
It's there, Cicero, it's there.I'm glad I got to meet Betty Dunson's son.
待在这里 好好的和你的未婚妻生活
You just stay here, Tommy.Enjoy your life with your beautiful bride...
在这些巨大的松树下面
amongst these majestic pine trees.
我们走！
Let's go!
我擦 这太不友好了
Well, that was uncool.
小白飞刀 你该休息了
White Knife, you must rest.
我怎能休息 如果到时他们到了风车那里 发现没有钱 会杀了我父亲的
How can I rest? When they get to the singing windmill and find no money, they will kill him.
孩子 松树太多 时间太紧迫了
My son, there are too many trees and too little time.
那我就要从其他途径获得这笔钱了
Then I must get this $50,000 another way.
什么途径 偷吗 这太不正直了
How? By stealing? There is no honor in that.
那我也可以从那些不正直的人那儿偷钱
Unless I steal from those who have no honor.
哦 这样就没什么问题了
Ooh... I like that.
但这样太危险了
But it is too dangerous.
我会派最勇敢的10名勇士帮助你
I will send ten of our strongest braves with you.
千万不要 印第安人在白人的世界里太危险了
No. The braves would be treated too cruelly in the white man's world.
莫事 很多勇士脸白 可以混淆过去 而且有个孩子还能很好地模仿白人的动作
A lot of them can pass for pale face. Raging Bear can actually do a great impression of a white guy.
让我们下会棋 再吃薯条吧
Hey, guys, let's play with our chest hair and eat potato chips.
不错吧 这不知道这熊孩子在哪里看到的
Wasn't that great? Where does he come up with this stuff?
是很不错 但是这事我必须一个人去了断
That's very good, Bear, but I must walk this path alone.
亲爱的 我会弄到钱 然后带去风车那里 等我回来参加我们的婚礼
My love... I will get this money...bring it to the singing windmill,and be back in time for our wedding.
我不会让你走的 这些人都是杀手
I won't let you go.Those men are killers.
我曾经的懦弱害死了母亲 这次我不会连累我父亲
I was a coward once and my mother paid the price.That will not happen to my father.
早上好
Morning
你从哪里冒出来的？
Where in the hell did you come from?
我遇到了点麻烦 我骑马到这里淘金 结果半路我的马死了
I'm in a bit of a bind, boys.I rode all the way out here to pan for gold and my horse up and died on me.
马怎么死的?
How'd he die?
自杀 在它小溪喝水的时候 头一直不抬起来把自己给淹死了 太惨了
Suicide. Drowned himself.Put his head in the stream and just kept it there.Saddest thing you ever seen.
常有的事 虽然不想承认 但这傻逼事就是会发生
It happens.Powers that be don't like to admit it, but it happens.
他看起来像是个诚实的白人 跳上来把
He looks like an honest white guy.Hop on.
感激不尽
Much obliged.
我在最近的一个镇上下就可以了
Just drop me off at the nearest town.
女士先生们 来来来 这是我最新发明的护理精油 包治百病
Ladies and gentlemen, gather around.Hear the wondrous effects of Dr.Chubb's Vita Oil,the miracle cure for 1001 ailments.
只要滴上一滴...你就马上...这谁啊这?
Put the pep back in your...Who's this asshole?
看 那个人居然在马槽里面喝水
Well, now, look at this fella,drinking from the horse trough.
那谁谁 你这样做 看着太让人作呕了
Excuse me.You there!What you're doing is disgusting.
这是牲口才喝的水
That water is for our filthy horses.
水是大自然给我们的恩惠 谁都可以喝 对吧老兄？
Water flows from the sky spirit for all its children.Isn't that right, cousin?
你那些歪门邪说在我们这里不管用 明白？"老兄"
We don't cotton to that peyote-smoking nonsense around these parts.Do you hear me, "cousin"?
算了 William 别跟他废话
Okay,William, come on back.
喂 小伙子 你打算留在镇上吗？
Hey, amigo.You planning on staying in town?
可能需要一个地方躺会儿
Might need a place to lay my head for a bit.
刚才那个男人那样说你 太不像话了
Sorry about that ugly man that insulted you.
他开了家银行 觉得自己理所当然可以对人霸道无理
He runs the bank, so he thinks he's entitled to be mean to everyone.
镇上有家银行？
There's a bank in this town?
为何这样问 难不成你还想抢银行呢？
Why? You wanna rob it?
夫人 我看起来难像抢银行的？
I look like a bank robber to you, ma'am?
很奇特啊 你让我想起来某个银行抢劫犯
Funny, there's something about you that reminds me of a certain bank robber.
他的名字叫Frank Stockburn
His name was Frank Stockburn.
你认识Frank Stockburn？
You know Frank Stockburn?
认识？没有见过面那种?
"Know"? Like, in the biblical sense?
不是 夫人 你以前亲自见过他吗?
No, ma'am. You've met him before is what I'm asking.
是的 我见过他
Yes, I met him.
认识他20分钟后 我在床上"见过”了他 就在那里
Then, 20 minutes later,I knew him in the biblical sense on that bed, right there.
接着 在这个扶手旁 我又“见过”了他2次
And, I knew him, in the biblical sense, twice on this railing.
然后 我们又倒立着"见面" 就在你靠着的梳妆台那里
And then, while doing a handstand on that dresser you're leaning against.
他有没有提起过一架会唱歌的风车？
Did he happen to mention a singing windmill?
他确实提起过一架会唱歌的风车 他说听起来就像天使的合唱一样
He did mention a singing windmill.He said it sounded like a choir of angels.
他有没有说风车在哪儿？
Where'd he say it was?
他说在那里 赢得了他人生中最大的一次比赛 然后就笑了
He said that it was in a place where he made his biggest score. Whatever that was,then he laughed.
他很喜欢笑
He liked to laugh...
还有倒立的性爱
and have handstand sex.
呃 这个可以pass掉
Yeah, we gotta get past that.
我很想念他 不过他确实留下了一件纪念品
I miss him.But he did leave me something to remember him by.
什么纪念品？
What's this?
niño,Ramon.
我还有一个兄弟？
I have a brother?
Burro 好兄弟 我们在一起这么久了 虽然都在慢慢变老 但是我们一起经历的冒险旅途 都是宝贵的记忆
Oh, Burro, we had many adventures together, you and me.We're not getting any younger.At least we have our memories.
记得在南达科他州的那2个姐妹吗？ 我知道你喜欢更肥的那只 哈哈哈 不要不承认
Remember the two girls,the sisters, in Deadwood?You liked the fat one.You know it's true.
Ramon Lopez?
我是
我刚刚见过你的母亲 结果... 偶然发现 你的父亲和我的父亲...
I just came from conversating with your mother, Esmerelda.We stumbled upon the fact that your dad and my dad...
是同一人...
are the same fella.
真是开门见山
Oh, that's neat.
简洁如我
Yeah
同一个父亲 那我们就是同父异母的兄弟 你怎么看 Burro?
Same father.Half-brothers.What do you think about that, Burro?
那么 我们父亲怎么样？
So, how is Dad?
他被绑架了 我需要筹够5万元 才能救他的命
Well, he went and go himself kidnapped,and I need to come up with $50,000 to save his life.
需要这么多银子？
That's a lot of pesos.
可不是吗 所以我决定抢劫镇上的银行
Sure is.That's why I'm fixin' to rob the bank here in town.
等一下 你意思是 我的父亲遇到了麻烦？
Hang on.My father is in trouble.
我的兄弟又需要我的帮忙
My brother, he needs my help.
我和你一起去抢银行
I'll rob the bank with you.
我必须独自完成这事儿
I must do this alone.
你要干嘛 兄弟
What's happening right now?
当我还是小孩子的时候 我就期待有一天见到我的父亲 一起吃饭 把他介绍给我的驴子朋友
Ever since I'm pequeño,I dream about spending one magical day with mi padre,sharing meals, introducing him to the burro.
除非你答应让我帮你 不然我不会松手的
I will not let go of you until you say I can help you.
如果你停止用刷子刷我 我就答应你
Will you stop brushing me if I say yes?
当然可以
Yes.
那你可以帮我忙
Then you can help.
它打屁意味着喜欢你
That means he likes you.
女士 你需要借的这笔款项不是小数目 通常情况下 我们会要求你出示2份证明
That's a good amount of money you want us to lend you.Now, normally, we would require two forms of identification, madam,
但是您这种大美女就不需要了
but that won't benecessary in your case.
Burro 想到要从好人这里抢钱 我感到好愧疚
I feel kinda guilty about this, Burro,taking money from nice people.
你幸好不是那种看起来脏兮兮的墨西哥人
I mean, it's not like you're some greasy Mexican.
突然感觉没那么愧疚了
I feel less guilty now.
你在干什么！这里是银行！赶紧把那头驴弄出去！
What are you doing?This is a bank!Get that donkey out of here!
先生 这是美国西部小毛驴
It is a burro, señor.
我不管这是什么傻逼玩意儿 “先生” 赶紧给我弄出去！
I don't care, "señor."Get it out!
行行 我们走吧...小毛驴不想走...
All right. Vámonos.The burro don't want to vámonos.
我才不管这头牲口想怎样！！
Well, I don't really care what the burro wants.
赶紧给我滚出去 你这个畜生！！！
Get out of my bank, you beast!
我知道你在想什么 但现在还不是时候 给我稳住
I know what you're thinking, but not yet.Hold it.
这个傻逼怎么会卡在这里 刚才它明明能从这里进来 现在怎么可能出不去了呢！！见了鬼了！！！
How is this jackass stuck?If it got in here, it can certainly get out!It doesn't make sense, it's not logical.
他们把钱藏的真好
They got it locked up good, do they?
我操 我不信还治不了你了！！！
Oh! You are leaving!
看啊 那个傻逼摔了个狗吃屎!
Gall dang, 1he felled on his pooper!
这太特么不正常了!
That makes no sense!
很...很抱歉...我马上弄它走...
I apologize.- I don't know how many times I could...
朋友好啊 需要我帮忙把它弄出来吗？
Hey, friend.Need any help gettin' her out?
她不是真的被卡住了 我的朋友 她只是用来分散注意力的
She's not really stuck,amigo.She's just a diversion.
她是处女？刚好我也是处男...
She's a virgin?I'm a virgin, too...
从不是很严格的意义上说
unless you count canty-loupes.
我相信你 小处男 听着 这头驴是用来分散银行老板注意力的 我的兄弟才好去偷银行的钱
I believe that, but she's a diversion to keep the banker busy so that my brother has time to rob the bank.
你们要抢银行?? 太牛逼了！!
You're robbin' the bank?Gall dang!
大事不妙！ Virgil 快吧钥匙给我！！
No! Virgil! Virgil, the key!
我的名字小皮特
叫I'm Lil Pete.
那你爸的名字就叫大皮特咯？
So, is your father, like, Big Pete?
我没见过我的粑粑 但他和你们一样都是银行抢劫犯 他叫Frank
I didn't know my pa.But he was a bank robber like y'all! His name was Frank.
姓Stockburn
Stockburn?
你怎么知道？？难不成你是巫师？？！！
How'd you know?Are you a wizard?
“儿子 我们会在Jawbone大瀑布那里等你 你的父亲留”
Frank Hey, Johnny Law.We'll be waiting for you up at Jawbone Falls.Frank Stockburn.
来人啊 来人啊 有人在抢银行！！！
Robbery!We're being burgled!
原来是你！！你就是那天喝我马槽水的那个人！！
You! Horse-water-drinker!
你被逮捕了！！
You are caught, sir!
你特么到底谁啊！！
What are you?
大哥 你猜怎么着？我又找到了一个失散多年的弟弟
Hey, Tommy, guess what? We got ourselves a little brother.
都是 我们的母亲都被同一个抢银行的给哼哼了 是不是很赞啊！！
Yeah! All our moms got porked by the same outlaw. Ain't that a pip
对 我很赞同
Yeah, that's something.
大家来看啊 这些土匪刚刚把银行抢了
Hey! Those bandidos just robbed the bank!
吃我枪子儿把 你们这些肮脏的外国佬
Taste my bullets, you dirty foreigners!
就是现在！！！
Now!
Burro 干的好！
Nice one, Burro
他们在那里！！
There they are!
我们得赶紧逃
We better make tracks.
我能加入你们吗 我有辆马车
Can I come with? I got a wagon.
没问题 我觉得可以有 我们走！！
All right, that ain't a bad idea, let's go.
如果你们是我兄弟的话 你们是不是也和我一样 有3颗奶头？
So, if you guys are my brothers,you must got three nipples, too.
我只有2颗
I only got two.
对 我也只有2颗
Yeah, just got the two.
呃 那肯定是我妈遗传给我的 当我没说
Oh, must be from my mama's side.Forget I tolded you that, okay?
莫问题呀
Will do.
Clem 你准备好了吗？
Are you ready, Clem?
恩恩 我准备好了...
Yep, yep. I'm... I'm ready.
这勺子...看着真锋利啊...
Spoon. Damn sharp
听着大伙儿 我真的想和你们一起去追捕那个白人印第安人 但是我的眼睛有点问题
Look, fellas, I wanna hunt this white Injun down same as you.I have some problems with my eyes.
你如果想真心加入"左眼帮派"的话 你就必须挖出你的右眼
You wanna join the Left-Eye Gang,that right eye has gotta come out.
疼一会会就不疼了
It'll only hurt for a second.
就是 就疼那么一小小会
Yeah, like a hundred seconds.
然后你就正式加入我们了
Then you're one of us.
一辈子的好基友
For life.
好吧 听起来有道理...
Okay, that makes sense.
我...能不能...把左眼挖出来 本来左眼视力就不是很好 但是右边的视力很好 如果挖掉的话是不是太可惜了...?
Is it okay if I scoop this left eye out?This is... I'm basically blind here.This right one sees like an eagle.Yeah, it just seems like a waste that I'd...
我明白你的难处 但是这是规定
I understand your predicament but rules is rules.
好吧 这我了解...
Yeah, it... makes sense.
这样做是不是有点过分了...
That ain't right!
挖了一半掉在那里了 还连着血管...
It's half way there...dangled by a van
太疯狂了 这样我还看得见
It's crazy, I can still see out of it!
天哪 我快吐了
I think I'm gonna puke.
像是黏在脱衣舞女奶子上的流苏一样
It's just going round and round like a tassel on a stripper's titty!
马上就好了 马上就好了
Ok gotta get it gotta get it
我不行了 我快晕了
I'm getting dizzy!
恭喜你成功了 欢迎成为我们左眼帮派的一员！
You done it, partner. Welcome to the Left-Eye Gang.
我做到了！
I did it!
太好了 我终于做到了！
I'm glad that's done.
现在我们一起去追捕那个喜欢印第安人的白人吧
Let's just go get that Injun-loving son of a bitch, huh?
赞同 我们现在出发吧
Yeah! Let's get him. Yeah.
哦 我不小心摸到眼窝了 操！
Oh, I touched the hole.I touched the hole!
我现在也是有眼罩的人了
Got me a patch!
亲爱的麻麻 自从我上次去买了一个冰淇淋后就消失了 你是不是觉得很奇怪捏
Dear Mama,you may be wondering why I have not returned from my trip to the ice cream store.
那是因为我遇到我的兄弟 Ramon 和 Tommy  我们现在准备去偷钱
It's because I met my brothers, Ramon and Tommy.And we're trying to steal money.
因为我们的粑粑被坏淫抓走了 带到了一架会唱歌的风车那里 所以我们需要钱去救他
We need the money to give to the bad men who took Pa away to the land of the singing windmill.
Tommy 说我们不能去偷正直人的钱 幸好西部有太多不正直的人了
Tommy says it's not okay to take money from decent folks. Luckily, there's a lot of bad people here in the West.
吃吧 享受地吃吧 我知道你喜欢的啦
Eat it! You know you like it.You know you like it.
我的个天
Good God!
真是一头"好"驴子啊
Good burro!
对对对... 就这样...
That's right.Enjoy it!
这也太特么恶心了
That's just wrong.
这个萝卜比香瓜好使多了 哈哈哈
This is so much better than the cantaloupe.
哈哈哈哈 小毛驴真是好样的
Good burro!
慢慢地 我们快筹集到了救粑粑的5万美金了 偶从来没见过这么多钱啊 妈妈
Slowly, but surely,we're chippin' away at the $50,000 we need to save Pa.That's a lot of money, isn't it, Mama?
我在干什么？ 哦 哈哈哈 我想起来了 我给你写信 妈妈 哈哈 我已经迫不及待想见我的粑粑了
Mama? Oh, yeah, that's right.I'm writing you a letter.Anyways, I can't wait to actually meet my pa.
我想让粑粑教我如何生孩子 女淫们怎样拉屎屎的 我会尽快赶回来 爱你的蠢儿子
I want him to teach me how you make babies.And how the lady poops 'em out.Be home quick as I can.}Your loving son, Lil Pete.
Tommy?
肿么了？我的弱智弟弟？
Yeah, Lil Pete?
这个会唱歌的风车到底在哪里？
Where's the singing windmill?
粑粑在那里赢得了最大的一次比赛
It's where dad made his biggest score.
或许我们去Jawbone大瀑布那里可以找到一些线索 粑粑以前被通缉时经常躲在那里
Maybe we'll get another clue up at Jawbone Falls.That's where he used to hide out when he was an outlaw.
太棒啦！！
Oh, cool beans.
Tommy?
又怎么了 我的弱智蠢弟弟？
Yeah, Lil Pete?
如果我们被抓住了 是不是很麻烦？
If we get caught stealing...would we be in trouble?
我们会被绞死的
I reckon we'll hang.
恩...那我没什么问题了  我的脖子很结实的
Well... that's no bother.I got a real strong neck.
以前我功课没有按时完成的话 妈妈就会惩罚我 把耕地的犁套在我脖子上 然后耕地
Mama makes me pull the plow with my head if I don't finish my schoolwork.Which occurs regularilly.
硬脖子总有一天派上用场 我们现在睡了吧
Strong neck might come in handy.Okay, let's get our rest.
晚安啦 Tommy
Good night, Tommy.
晚安 蠢弟弟
Good night, Lil Pete.
晚安 Ramon
Good night, Ramon.
晚安 兄弟们
Good night, brothers.
晚安 我的小毛驴
Good night, Burro.
打的屁是干的 明天会是个好天气
That's a dry one.We will have good dry weather tomorrow.
走开！ 该死的苍蝇！走开！！
Shoo, fly!Shoo!!
赶紧走开 死苍蝇 不要打扰我们睡觉！
Oh, come on, fly, vámonos! We need our sleep.
让我把它解决了
Let me take care of this.
黑漆漆的你怎么看得见？
How can you see a fly in the dark?
一个真正的猎者是感官并用的
A true hunter sees with all his senses.
你真有一手 佩服
That was some mystical shit, man.
我觉得你刚才是把苍蝇的食物打掉了
I think you just nicked his biscuits off.
我就是这样做的
That's what I was aiming for.
它用不着死 它需要知道的是它在这里并不受欢迎
He didn't deserve to die.He deserved to know he was not welcome here.
不愧是被印第安人抚养大的 你有着他们的思想
Raised by Indians, huh?That had some impact on you.
让我来解决这一只
Well, let me get this one.
听起来像马蝇一样
Sounded like a horse fly.
那不是马蝇 那是我的马！！
That wasn't a horse fly, that was my horse!
Peanut?
Oh, Peanut!
现在我的小毛驴该遭殃了...
Oh, the burro's gonna be pissed.
小毛驴 你做的很好 不要怕你旁边的马 你和它做的一样好！
You're doing bueno,Burro!Don't be intimidated by the horse,you're just as good as him.
哥哥们 我好饿啊！
I'm so hungry.
周围有很多吃的啊 坚果啊 浆果啊 树皮 以及各种泥土
There's breakfast all around.Nuts, berries, bark,different kinds of mud.
如果附近有塔可树就好了
I wish there were taco trees.
塔可是什么东东？
What's a taco?
墨西哥煎饼卷 把肉末 起司 番茄酱都夹在薄皮卷里 超级好吃
They're the best.Meat and cheese and tomatoes in a crispy shell.You'd love it, man.
啊啊啊 我受不了了 我要一口气吃50个
Ooh, I want one. I want 50.
兄弟们 不得不打断你们 我们到了 Jawbone 大瀑布
Hate to put an end to this fascinating conversation, but we're here, Jawbone Falls
旁边还居然有间房子
And there's a mansion next to it!
我们干脆直接进去吧
Should we just go in?
我赞成
I reckon.
呵呵哒 这里看着真舒服
haha this is cozy
不要伤害我的哥哥们!!!
Don't hurt my brother!
不要怕 我们只是来找我们的父亲的
We don't mean no harm.just looking for our dad.
这是你的家吗？... 那这是谁的家？|
Is this your place?Whose place is it?
这是你的妈妈家？
Your mother?
噢 那她现在在家吗？
Oh, is she here right now?
哦 她已经去世了 我很抱歉 她肯定是位好母亲
Oh, she's dead.I'm so sorry, I'm sure she was a good woman.
她三年前去世的？
She died three years ago?
三个月前?!
Three months ago?
噢 我知道了 你妈妈有3个奶头！！
Oh, your mama has three nipples?
对对 我们有3个人
Yeah, there's three of us.
你和你妈妈不会是在这里非法酿酒吧？
You and your mom were making moonshine up here, huh?
你们非法酿的酒商标是...Frank Stockburn?!
Making moonshine for... Frank Stockburn?
你认识 Stockburn？
You know Frank Stockburn?
他在这里呆过？和你妈妈在一起过？
He slept here?With your mama?
哦哈哈 我看懂了 你的妈妈是只猫头鹰!
Your mama was an owl.
才不是呢 蠢弟弟 是我们的粑粑把她麻麻弄出了那样的声音
No, our dad made his mom make owl noises.
很对 朋友 确切来说 应该是叫你 我们的兄弟
Yeah, that's right, friend.We're your brothers.
来来来 干杯 干杯
Down the hatch, boys!Salud. Salud.
你有名字吗?
What's your name, anyways?
H... R... M...
我们干脆叫你Herm好了
How 'bout we just call you Herm?
Herm 我们之所以来这 是因为我们的粑粑被坏淫们绑架了
Herm, so you know,our dad was kidnapped by some bad muchachos.
都是 我们需要大笔的银子赎回老豆
we need money to get him back
所以我们决定去偷钱
So we're going to steal the money.
准确来说 我们只去偷坏淫们的钱
No, we're only stealing the money from folks what are bad.
你知道附近有没有坏人 我们好去偷他们的钱？
So do you know of any place where we could steal a lot of money from some bad folks?
大金块酒吧？
The Gold Nugget Saloon, huh?
你要和我们一同去吧
I reckon you're coming with us?
小狐狸担心小白飞刀 寝食难安 她必须得吃点东西
Smoking Fox so worried about White Knife.We must get her to eat something.
哟 看谁在这里吃午餐呢
Oh, we having a little picnic here, huh?
你们没有权利来这里 这是我们印第安人的地盘！
You have no right to be here! This Apache land!
那你又能怎么着我呢 海狸鼠？
And what you gonna do about it, beaver breath?
他怎么知道我的名字？
How he know my name?
我操 这真是她的名字！
That's really her name!
我觉得你应该叫“巫婆" "猪肉荣"或者是"呕吐脸"
Yeah, I think you also could havegone with "Face Like Witch."Or "Eats Like Pig."Or "Hit In Face With Diarrhea Stick."
没了 就这些绰号？ 没其他的了？
That's it? Nobody else?Babyface? Stumbles?
头儿 看啊！我抓住了谁！！！哈哈这下我们拿小白飞刀有辙了
Hey, boss!Look what I got here!He ain't gonna be happy about this.
这个小镇以前是很繁荣的 后来金子被挖完了 连火车都不运行了
Yep, used to be a prosperous town.Then the gold mine dried up and the train stopped stopping.
但是那家酒吧生意一直很好 从开业以来生意一直很好 从早到晚都是人 从来没有关门过
The saloon's the only place left that still does a good business.Open day and night since they built it. Ain't even a lock on the front door.It never closes.
他们在酒吧里面的壁炉里挂了一个很大的金块 人们总是来参观 据说金块至少值---20000美元
They got a big ol' golden nugget hanging above the fireplace.Folks come from all over just to take a look.They say it's worth about $20,000, easy.
我很惊奇居然没有人会去偷那块金子
I'm surprised no one's ever tried to stolen that nugget.
有人试过啊 但是没人成功过 酒吧吧台上挂的全部是失败者的手指 酒店老板干的事情 所以没人敢惹他
Oh, folks have tried.If you go in there, you see their thumbs hanging above the bar.Smiley Harris, the owner, bit them clean off.So nobody messes with Smiley.
感觉像搔痒痒一样
That sort of tickled.
你有什么问题吗 打开你的袍子 我来瞧瞧...噢我从来没有看过这么大范围的皮疹 都感染成绿色了
What we got going over here, friend?Just open your robe, please.I have never seen that big of a rash...or infection or whatever this green bubble is.
骚年... 不论现在你在做什么... 都请停下来... 这样让我...我的手很难受...
Now, son, I would simply recommend that you stop doingwhatever it is you've been doing,with whoever...or whatever you've been doing it with.
知道为什么叫酒店老板Smiley吗？因为无论当他在做任何残忍的事情时候 他脸上都挂着一种诡异的微笑
Yep, now they call him Smiley,'cause even when committing the most unspeakable atrocities,a cheerful grin never leaves his face.
OK 请把你的屁股太高
All right, just lift yourtail for me, please.
因为如此 金块才未曾偷过 也不会被偷
Now, he's why that nugget has never been stolen.And never will be stolen.
涂上这个可以预防感染
This'll prevent infection.
尝起来味道不错捏
It tastes good, too.
这个叫Smiley的人听起来倒像是一个当地恶霸
This Smiley fella, sounds more like a hooligan than a barkeep.
就是这么回事 传说他以前是和Frank Stockburn 帮派一伙的
You're not far off.Rumor has it that back in the old dayshe used to run with the Frank Stockburn Gang.
要不要涂唇膏？
Lip balm?
不用了 谢谢
I reckon I'm good.
看来那个叫Smiley的人 不是那么简单
That Smiley fellow,he don't joke around.
噢  话说严重了 我平时很和蔼可亲的 只要不和我过不去
Oh... I joke around...but never when it comes to my business.
欢迎来到我的“大金块酒吧”
Welcome to the Gold Nugget, gentlemen.
哈里斯先生 久闻大名
Mr. Harris, it's quite a nice spread you got here.
什么风把你们几位吹来了？
So what brings you gentlemen to town?
事实上 哈里斯先生 我们来想向您打听点消息
Actually, we wanted to ask you about something, Mr. Harris.
我现在正在同这几位先生谈话 等会再和你交谈
I am conversing with these gentlemen, sir.I shall be with you in a moment.
我需要和你谈谈Frank Stockburn
I need to talk to you about Frank Stockburn.
我已经有很多年没有听到过这个名字了
I haven't heard that name in many a year.
这么说来你认识他
You know him.
Stockburn先生和我以前是生意伙伴
Mr. Stockburn and I were business partners.
我这里有张照片 看 这是他 这是你 你当时是他帮派中的一员吧
I got a photograph.You see, that there's him...and that's you.You rode in his gang.
准确来说 应该是我们共同的帮派
To be precise... it was our gang.
他在黑帮派里混的很出名 我做的却是正派的生意 也很成功
He went on to a criminal career of some renown,while I achieved great success in the legitimate business world.
请帮帮我
Please help me.
先生 你这样做有点过分了
Sir, you are becoming a nuisance.
我需要告诉他我做过些什么
I just need to tell him what I've done.
老板 差不多了 再不停手就要出人命了
I think he's had enough, boss.
确实 各位不好意思 我也不想弄成这样
Yes.My apologies, gentlemen.Not my favorite subject.
下一轮酒全部免费
A round on the house.
还有 Chico, 如果你下次再这样抓住我的手臂的话 我就让你吃6颗枪子儿
And, Chico, if you ever grab my arm like that again,I'll put six bullets in your head.
刚才你被打的好惨 没事吧？
That's quite a beating.Hope you and your drink are okay.
为什么你这么急切的想找到Frank Stockburn？
Why do you want to meet this Frank Stockburn so badly, huh?
因为他是我的父亲
Frank Stockburn's my father.
如果Frank Stockburn是你父亲的话 把手举起来
If Frank Stockburn is your father, raise your hand.
Chico是对的 到了晚上 人就少点了
Chico's right. Getting late, starting to thin out.
兄弟们 想给你们说点事情 不想我们之间有秘密
Can I tell you guys something?Because I don't wanna have no secrets between us.
-当然可以 -我们是兄弟嘛
-Of course. Yeah -we're brothers.Yeah.
你们看 我父亲是白人 但是我母亲是黑人 所以我是黑白混血儿
Now, I know Dad is a white man, but my mother...was actually black.So that, technically,makes me half-black.
你确定 兄弟？
Is that right?
我不想隐瞒你们我是黑人 不是纯种的白人 是不想以后你们无意中说出种族歧视的话
Well, I didn't wanna hide that from you in case you guys slipped up and made some racial slurs not knowing I wasn't 100% white.
我敢肯定你母亲很健壮 但是我不确定 她居然是个黑人
I mean, I knew she must've been really muscular,but I had no idea she was black.
既然你提起来了 我觉得你母亲好像就是黑人
Yeah, I mean, I guess,now that you mention it,I see it a little bit.
我的母亲是瑞典人
My mother's Swedish.
我不这么认为 我觉得她应该是墨西哥人
I don't think so. I reckon she's Mexican.
特么的 居然敢骗我
Lying bitch!
那么我的兄弟们 你们有什么本事 今天晚上能够帮上忙的？
So do you new brothers have any special skills that could help us out here tonight?
比如说呢？
Like what?
比如 Tommy是个用刀能手 小皮特有三个奶头 我有一头小毛驴
Like, you know, Tommy'sgood with knives. Lil Pete's got a bonus nipple.I got a burro.
Herm能一手把人给掐死
Herm is good at strangling.
我能在水下憋气6分钟
I can hold my breath for six minutes.
我能用鸡巴弹钢琴
Well, I can play the piano with my dick.
那么 我们就所向无敌了 我需要你们这些帅小伙来帮忙偷那块大金子
Well, we're unstoppable then.Anyways, any of you handsome brothers ready to go steal a big hunk of gold?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
我醉了
I'm drunk.
我是小皮特
And I'm Lil Pete.
(你在说什么鸟语 死胖子)
既然大家准备好了 我们就动手吧
Let's get that nugget then.
你还挺有种的 居然还敢来找我
You've got some pair of huevos coming into my place, son.
非常抱歉白天发生事情 哈里斯先生 作为补偿 我想用这笔钱...一瓶好酒
I sure am sorry about what happened, Mr. Harris.In fact, I'd like to buy you a drink...of the good stuff, if that's okay?
嘿 伙计 有没有从苏格兰来的 上等苏格兰酒？
barkeper you got any scotch real scotch, from scotch-land?
我们把上等的进口好酒都藏在后面 等我去取过来
We keep the imported stuff in the back.I'll go and fetch it for you.
好极了
That's wonderful.
我什么也没听见 你呢？
Now, I didn't hear that, did you?
事实上我听见了
I did.
我有点糊涂了 今天晚上是周五 墨西哥菜之夜吗 还是队列舞蹈之夜？
I don't know, maybe I'm turned round.I thought that, like, tonight was gonna be Fajita Friday or line dancing or something.
因为酒吧看起来很冷清啊 回见啊 大伙儿 多保暖
It just seems quiet, but y'all be good.Stay warm.
-他把老板的战利品手指都带走了！ -没有啊 是它们自己挂到我身上的
- Hey, he's got the thumbs!- They came with the pants!
向右边跑 向右边跑！
Right on the rocks, right on the rocks.
来啊来啊 快来抓我啊！
Oh, you're gaining on me!You're gaining on me!
抓住你就死定了 别跑！
You don't even understand\what we're gonna do to...
让你们好好瞧瞧不要惹我们Stockburn兄弟！！
Teach them not to mess with the Stockburn brothers!
我在看着你!
I'm watching you!
谁在说话？
Who's that?
打扰了 女士们
Ladies.
去看看3号门里面有什么？
What's behind door number three?
来吧 美女们 把衣服脱了 朝我脸上打一拳
Okay, ladies, take your clothes off and start punching me in the face.
不好意思 请继续
Sorry, carry on.
Smiley 来 到这里来看你的奶奶
Smiley, why don't you visit your grandma
来地狱！！！
In hell!
你逃不掉的 Smiley！！
You cannot escape me, Smiley!
把我的手指还给我！！
Give me my thumbs back.
小皮特 太大了！拉不上去！！
It's too big, Lil Pete!
什么太大了！！
What's too big?
呃...B计划太大了？？
Uh... plan B's too big?
B计划是特么什么东西！
What the hell is plan B?
等下你就知道了
Let me show you.
B计划！
Plan B!
忘了告诉你 要有刀才能做那个动作...
Yeah, works better if you have knives.
都是 不好意思 我忘鸟...
Yeah, that makes sense.
酒店老板疯了 看见谁都在射击
He's shooting like a madman!
谁动 我开枪打谁
Next man who moves will die!
你们到底是什么人？
Who are you people?
我们是Stockburn兄弟
We are the Stockburn brothers.
Frank的孩子们？...呵呵呵...这变得越来越有意思了
Frank's kids?Well... this is interesting.
我最后见你们的父亲是在犹他州 当时我们干了一笔大买卖
You know, the last time I saw your father was in Utah.Just rang up our biggest score.
结果我们在分赃的时候 有了分歧
But when we was dividing it up,we started having trouble with the arithmetic.
结果后来我被像狗一样扔在了一架风车旁 肚子上插了一把刀
And somehow I ended up abandoned beside a windmill,knife stuck in my guts,left to die like a dog.
Frank把所有的钱都卷跑了 但是现在上天给我报仇的机会...我要亲手杀了他可笑的5个孩子...
Frank had taken it all.But now, I get to take something.The lives of his five ridiculous sons.
不要忘了还有我！！！
Don't forget about número seis!
他向他自己的头开了6枪！！！
He's giving himself six bullets to the head!
他的头还在笑！
And he's still smiling!
其实我只是想把他敲晕而已
I was just trying to knock him out.
恭喜你 你成功了
Well, you succeeded.
只不过你把他“敲晕”以后 他不会醒过来了
I don't think he's waking up from that one.
来 Danny 这是古老的印第安疗法
Here you are, Danny.It's an old Apache remedy.
擦擦你的头 在宿醉以后最有效了
Clears your head after too much firewater.
你怎么知道这么多东西 Tommy 你到底在哪里学的
You know everything, Tommy.Where'd you learn all this stuff?
我的父亲教给我的
My father taught me.
父亲？不会吧！你不是上个星期才见到他的吗？
Dad? I thought you just met him last week.
不是我们的生父 是我的养父
Not our father. Screaming Eagle.
他从小抚养我成人 是我见过的最善良最智慧的人
He raised me since I was a kid.He's the kindest... wisest man I've ever known.
哇 有粑粑的赶脚真好
wow must've been nice to have a dad.
对头 可以陪你一起摔跤 还可以教你怎么切蛋糕
Oh, yeah, someone to wrastle with and teach you how to cut up your panny-cakes.
在你很惨的时候给予你建议
Someone to give you advice when you screwed up real, real bad.
没事 我们是有父亲的
Well, we do got a dad.
我们马上就可以见到他了
And we're gonna see him real soon.
恩 我都等不及要见他了
Yeah... I can't wait.
不用担心 我去看看怎么回事
ok boys I'm gonna check this out.
你们要这样拿着球 腿弯曲 然后把球扔出去 准备好了吗？！
The ball is in your hand, twist the leg, then you let it go!Now, let me see. Ready, men?
不是这样的！！认真听我说 你们这些亚洲人
No, no, no!You're not listening to me, Hung Shin!
你们必须动作准确 准确 再准...听见了吗
You have to be very precise.Precise...I say!
嘿 那边那群小伙子 我有一个提议
You there!I have a proposition.
要不一起来才参加一个即将诞生的伟大运动？
How would you men like to participate in the birth of something extraordinary?
不好意思 我们没时间 但是我们把你的球捡到了
Well, we ain't got time for that, but you can have your brown thing back.
什么事情如此重要 你们不知道错过的是什么? 历史的见证时刻
What's so damnably important that you need to miss your rendezvous with history?
我们要去救我们的粑粑   Frank Stockburn
We gotta save our daddy, Frank Stockburn.
Frank Stockburn 那个亡命之徒?
Frank Stockburn, the outlaw?
你认识我们的父亲？
You know our dad?
肯定了 扑克比赛的能手 我遇到过的最强的对手
Without a doubt.One of the best poker players I've ever played against.
当时我在亚利桑那州的当地扑克牌比赛和他遇见的 就在情人节当天
I played him in Ezekiel Grant's annual Valentine's Day game down in Yuma.
你们父亲连眼都没眨一下 就赢了几千美元
Thousands of dollars on the table, but Stockburn doesn't bat an eyelash.
他有没有提到他哪里赢得最大的比赛?
He happen to mention anythingabout what his biggest score was?
在亚利桑那州 有没有提到一个叫Smiley Harris的人?
Over in Utah? A guy named Smiley Harris?
这样吧 我和你们做个交易
I'll make you a deal.
帮我一个忙 我就会告诉你们我全部知道的
Help me out a bit and I'll tell you all I know.
成交 我叫Tommy Dunson
Deal. Tommy Dunson.
我叫Abner Doubleday 我们开始吧！
Abner Doubleday. Let's play ball.
欢迎大家来参加历史上史无前例的比赛 这个比赛规则是我一手创建的
Welcome, my friends, to the first ever playing of a new sport. A sport of my own devising.
比赛时 分为2队 每队10人 比赛内容是...
On this field, two ten-person teams will engage in a battle of...
有什么问题吗 奇先生？
Yes, Qi?
我们这里只有18个人
Only 18 people here.
每队分为9人 比赛内容考验大家的力量 速度 和策略
Two nine-person teams will engage in a battle of strength, speed, and strategy.
一队人进行防守 另外一队人用球进攻
One team will go out onto the field to play defense while the other team will take turns hitting this ball...
用木棍击打球
with a stickie.
这个比赛名称叫什么？
What are you gonna call this game?
还能叫什么？
What else?
Stickie McSchnickens.
每队的投球手的目标就是 我2次没有击中球 就赢了
Now your goal, ball thrower, is to get the ball past me two times without my hitting it.
准备好了就开始吧
Fire when ready.
我没想到你扔球的速度挺快的 好吧 没办法
I didn't know you were going to toss it quite so hard, ball thrower.All right.
好了 已经2次了 你输了 对吧？
Okay, that's two past ya. So you're done, right?
不行 我说了要得3次才行
No, no, I said three times.
不是 你说的就是2次
No, you said two.
不是！我说的是3次！3次击打成功我才出局！
I said three! Three strikes and I'm out.
我知道我说的什么 矮侏儒 (棒球里的游击手)
I know what I said, shortstop.
这是你的新名字 矮侏儒 对 就这个 你以后就叫这个名字了 永远不能改
That's your new name. Short Stop, that's right.Now and forever. Forever and ever!
矮侏儒 矮侏儒 矮侏儒 矮侏儒
Short Stop. Short Stop, Short Stop.Short Stop.
OK 我们开始下一轮吧
Yes, all right.
第3次击打成功！你出局了！！
Strike three! You're out!
不 不行 这个球扔的高度太低了
No, no, the ball was... too low.
要成功算接到一球的话 这个球的高度必须在...
In order for it to count as a strike, it has to pass through the...
击打范围之内
strike zone.
-击打范围之内？- Strike zone?
-是的 就是这样- That's right.
如果你击打球的高度不在我的膝盖和我胸部之间的话...
And if you don't get the ball past me, between my knees and my titties,
就不算成功扔球...就不算成功接球
it's not a strike....It's a non-strike.
如果你连着4次击打都不成功 那么我就毫不用力地赢得了第一垒
And if you throw me four non-strikes,I get an express ticket to first base without my even hitting it.
好勒 我们开始吧
All right, are we ready?
你犯规了 这样我也...赢得了第一垒
That also gets me to first base...as well.
你往哪儿跑 没人击中球啊？
Where you going? Nobody hit it.
我把垒给盗了 你没注意 我把它给盗了
I stole the base. You weren't looking, so I stole it.
你说过只有当你成功击中球的时候 你才能往前跑
You said you could only advance after you hit the ball!
但是盗垒的时候...不算
Not when you're stealing.
真是胡说八道
That's bullshit.
别冒泡 你这个矮侏儒
Okay, Short Stop.
他在你背后动了
He's moving!
我没动！
Safe!
这下好了 我们应该打成平手了
Gall dang, I don't know.That was a tie.
就是 我们打成平局了！
Yes, and tie goes to the runner!
为何是这样的
Why's that?
因为这个比赛规则是我一手创建的 这就是原因
Because those are the rules of Stickie McSchnickens, that's why.
成功了 我成功了！
All right, it's all mine, I've got it!
不是 根本不是这样！ 你不能跑 根据...内野高飞球规则
No! No, you can't run. You cannot run.Infield fly rule... in full effect.
你犯规出局了
You're out.
我才不会过去捡
Oh, I'm not getting that.
你应该环绕所有垒包跑 因为你打出了全垒打
You can just run all the way home. A home runner.
我需要一杯冷饮 我们中场休息5分钟 然后接着打下半场
I need a cold drink.Let's take a five-minute stretch and then start the second half.
Doubleday先生 我们真的不能陪你玩了
Mr. Doubleday, we're done.
但是我们才打9局啊
But we've only played nine innings.
9局足够了 我们的父亲在哪里赢得他人生中最大的比赛的
Nine innings is enough. Tell us about Dad's biggest score.
那好 你们父亲和他的帮派 打败了一个120人的骑兵队
Fine.Your father and his gang knocked off an entire cavalry regiment, 120 men,
并且扛走了足足5大箱美元钞票
five trunks filled with Yankee money.
在哪里发生的？
Where'd that happen?
一直朝着正前方走 100英里 在一个叫“甜蜜之猪”的岩石旁边 到了那里你就看到了
Up at Sweet Hog Rock...100 miles due north.You'll know it when you see it.
好吧 兄弟们 看来我要在那块岩石旁边找到 会唱歌的风车了
Well, fellas,looks like we're going to Sweet Hog Rock to find ourselves a singing windmill.
但是我们还差1000美元啊
But we still need another 10,000 bucks.
那我们就还要干上一笔了
I reckon we'll make a quick stop, then.
在你们离开之前 你们想不想和对方握手并且说“干的好 兄弟”？
Before you go...do you wanna line up and shake hands and say "good game" to each other?
不想
No.
那群小伙子其实人不错 当时给我现金就走人了 也没闯什么祸
Them boys were nice fellers.Paid in cash. Kept the profanity to a minimum.
你确定？ 我听说有个墨西哥人用铲子把这个恶霸的头都给砍了下来？
And the Mexican brother knocked this hard-ass' head off with a shovel?
这个老鬼的头足足被铲飞了40英尺
Dang thing flew nearly 40 feet!
都还在笑
And still a-smilin'.
我天 我去！！！
Oh! Man!
直到现在都在笑
And hasn't stopped yet.
不会吧...大哥... 用胶水能粘的起来？
Oh, hell, no! My man gluing on heads and shit!
希望到时候我鸡巴断了 他能给我粘的回来
Wish he'd glue the head back on my pecker.
你的小鸡吧怎么了？
What happened to your pecker?
我当时参加这个帮派之前 是混另外一个帮派的 在德州发生了一些不愉快的事情
I was part of another gang before I joined up with y'all.Texas Stubbies.
我说你们都不用愁了
Okay, never mind all that. Okay?
医生 告诉我们 那6个蠢货往哪个方向走了？
Now, Doc, you know which way them there Ridiculous 6 rode off to?
我们有一个朋友 需要和他们碰面
We're traveling with a friend of theirs who, uh... will be real excited to see them.
他们往绿松石山脉去了 我给你们在地图上指指
Well, they headed up north to the Turquoise Trail.I can show you on the map over here.
小狐狸 急着去见你老公吗？没用的 到时候他会跪地向我们求饶的
Looking forward to seeing your man beg for his life?'Cause that's what's gonna happen, Smoking Fox.
你老公就是个胆小鬼
Chicken pox!
我们马上就要找到他了 谁让他给印第安人一伙儿
We're gaining on his Injun-loving ass every day.
和我们左眼帮派  作对的下场就是：
He messed with the Left-Eye Gang!He's gonna be like,
"你们如何找到我的？...你们怎么抓住我老婆的？“
"Wait, how did you find me, and where...How did you get my girl?"
到时候这个愚蠢的小白飞刀就会意识到一切都太晚了 哈哈哈
And then old Dumb Knife's gonna realize that he's in way over his head.
当时华盛顿创建了美国的时候...
See, when George Washington invented America...
你好 警官 这个镇上有教堂吗?
Excuse me, Sheriff. Is there a church in this town?
怎么可能有？这里是美国西部最乱 最邪恶 最混乱的小镇
最This is Rattler's Gulch, you halfwit.The meanest, crookedest, most hellacious town in the West.
我们不需要那些牧师来告诉我们该做什么 不该做什么
We don't need no preacher telling us what we can and cannot do.
那是不是我就可以这样对你的老婆？
So it's all right if I do this to your wife?
绞我的时候 我都迫不及待想看你们的表情啦！！
I can't wait to see all you nice people when I'm dangling!
你这个变态的混蛋 赶紧把他给绞死
You sick bastard.Get this over with.
今天便宜你们了 等会好好看我表演哦
You're in for a real treat today. This is gonna be so much fun.
我和你们闹着玩儿的 我特么好着呢
I'm just messing with y'all. I'm fine!
我把介个动作叫做“脱离水的鱼"
I call this one Fish Out of Water.
Herm 把妓女们放回去...快点！！！
Herm, put the hookers back.Come on!
哈哈哈 你们抓不到我的 哈哈哈
Yeah, you can't catch me!
你看看 他根本不会死 他在戏弄你!!!
Look at him. He ain't dying, Billy! He's making a fool of you!
够了 我们开枪把这个傻逼打死！！
All right, that's it!We'll shoot the son of a bitch!
听我的指令 准备...
On my command!Ready
风把绳子吹歪了 我们就差一点就够着他了！
Wind took him, Tommy. Came damn close.
我莫事儿 甭管我...！
I'm okay!
我们成功了！！
We did it!
给你说过我脖子很结实吧 呵呵哈哈奥！
I told ya I got a strong neck!
我们必须比他们提前到达红猪岩石 而且还要找到会唱歌的风车才算了事
We still gotta get to Sweet Hog Rock before they do.Gotta find that singing windmill, so it ain't over yet.
我们终于把钱弄齐了！是我们6兄弟一起干的！！！耶耶耶！！！！！！！
We got the money!The Ridiculous 6 got all the money!
Tommy! Tommy! 父亲是怎样一个人 他幽默吗？
Tommy! Tommy! What's Dad like? Is he funny?
是好的倾诉对象吗？
Yeah, is he a good listener?
他强壮吗？
Is he strong?
你们问的都很好  我这样给你们说吧
All great questions. I'll tell you this.
我觉得你们肯定会喜欢父亲的 而且父亲也会很爱你们
I think you guys are gonna love him.But I'm sure he's gonna love you guys.
真不好意思打扰这个温馨的场面
So sorry to interrupt such a tender moment.
好像我们打扰人家洗澡了
Looks like we stumbled on bath day, boys!
硬汉们 我听说一路上你们认了不少兄弟是伐
I heard you picked up some brothers along the way, tough guy.
但是我发现你们怎么长的一点都不像呢？
But I don't see no resemblance.
我觉得倒是挺像 都长得像我的屁股眼儿 哈哈哈
I do, they all look like my butthole.
兄弟们 猜猜我们要对他们干什么？
So guess what time it is, boys?
报仇时间到！
Payback time!
有任何遗言吗 小白“没”刀？ 哈哈哈
Any last words, No Knife? [Laughs]
给你们说过我憋气时间很长的！
I told ya I could hold my breath good.
干得好 Danny 小子！！
Yeah, Danny boy!
你还在干嘛 我们得走了！
What are you doing, man?We gotta go!
钱是我们的！！！！！
That's ours!!
Rusty！！！我的马儿 快肥来！！！
Rusty? Rusty no!! come back!
现在我们怎么救粑粑啊 钱全部没了 还得重新筹
How are we gonna save him? We're startin' all over.
有没有其他地方我们还可以抢劫钱的？
Is there any more good places we can rob?
比如附近有喂驴子或者给她穿驴掌的地方?
You know like a burro-grooming place or a shoe store for burros?
西部一半的警力都在追捕我们
Half the lawmen in the west are already looking for us.
那又怎样 我们不能停下来就范 我们父亲会没命的
So what? Look, we can't stop.They're going to kill him!
没用的 他已经快不行了
Ain't no difference. He's dying anyways.
父亲生病了
Dad's sick.
对不起我没给你们说 很有可能他现在已经死了
I'm sorry I didn't tell y'all.There's a good chance he's dead already.
但是有可能父亲还没死呢 Tommy 我们必须去见他
But there's a chance he's not.You got to meet him, Tommy.
我们就算只能见到他5分钟 也算是值了
The rest of us...Even if it was just for five minutes, it'd be worth it.
如果我不向父亲倾诉我的秘密的话 我会死不瞑目的
If I don't talk to Dad, I'll die with this dirty secret burnin' a hole in my guts.
Danito 无论你做了什么 你都要原谅自己
Danito, whatever it is you did, you have to forgive yourself, man.
如果你知道我做了什么 你就不会这样说了
You wouldn't say that if you know what I done.
Danny 每个人都有秘密
Everybody's got secrets, Danny.
我就只跟你们说了我是黑人 这种感觉超爽
You guys are the first people I told I was black.You know how good that made me feel?
我们是你的兄弟 你可以给我们讲任何事情
We're your brothers.You can tell us anything.
我曾经为美国总统工作
I used to work for the President of the United States.
我曾是他的个人保镖
I was his personal bodyguard.
在一个夜晚之前 我都是他最好的保镖
One of the best.Till one night...
总统先生 我想去上个卫生间
Mr. President, say, I'm gonna go hit the little boys' room.
你特么在逗我吧？
Are you shitting me?
不要担心 没事儿的 就一小会
Come on! You'll be fine, superstar.
回来给你带点儿什么？水还是啤酒？
Can I get ya something on the way back? Agua? Brewski?
什么都不需要！
No!
林肯夫人 我给您带点饼干或者一个枕头吧 这场秀挺长的
Mrs. Lincoln, how about one of them big pretzels or a little pillow?I hear this play's kind of a long one.
那好吧 我马上就回来
All right, fair enough.I'll be back in two.
总统先生的包厢在哪里？
Where's the president's box?
你是那个演员John Wilkes Booth吗？
John Wilkes Booth, the actor?
这么巧 我是你的忠实粉丝！
No way, man! Big fan!
你是来见总统先生的吗？
You wanna say hi to the president?
他正在里面欣赏表演呢 左手边最后一间
He'd get a real kick out of that.Last door on the left.
哇哦 好喜欢这个演员
Wow! Love that guy!
"伤害了那么多人以后 你居然可以过得逍遥自在？"
How can you go on living your life knowing you harmed so many people?
我就想问父亲这个问题
That's what I wanna ask Dad.
嘿 别难过了 又不是你开的枪
Hey, you ain't the one who pulled that trigger.
如果你真的需要问父亲这个问题的话...我们就去筹集钱吧
But if Dad's gotta be the one who tells you that...then let's go get that money.
只不过我现在不知道在哪儿去弄这笔钱
I just wish I knew how.
Herm有个主意
Herm's got an idea.
他就是不知道如何表达
He just can't express it.
如果这里有人能听懂他说的话就好了
I just wish somebody here could speak Herm.
明天是情人节
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Ezekiel Grant会举行一年一度的赌注很大的扑克牌比赛
That's when Ezekiel Grant has his annual high-stakes poker game.
那里将有大量的钱 数不清的钱！！
There'll be oodles of money there. Oodles, I say.
我不确定这个方案是否可行 听起来很冒险
I don't know. That sounds risky.
什么很冒险
What's risky?
他提出我们去抢Ezekiel Gran开设的扑克牌比赛上的赌金
He's suggesting we... knock off Ezekiel Grant's poker game.
在亚利桑那州 明晚
It's in Yuma tomorrow night.
我们走半天就能到\Yuma's less than a day's walk from here.
那个比赛 足足有一支军队在站岗
That poker game, there's practically gonna be an army protectin' it.
如果Tommy说我们能够打败他们 我绝对相信他
If Tommy says we can beat'em, I'll believe him.
我们都会相信他
We all will.
我们能够打败他们 为了父亲
We can beat 'em...for Dad.
为了我们的父亲！
For Dad!
Ezekiel 我希望你能喜欢我为你准备的情人节礼物
I hope you like the gift I'm giving you for Valentine's Day, Ezekiel.
给你个提示吧 一个小时的免费按摩服务
I'll give you a hint. one-hour massage, no charge.
噢 Susannah 你知道我最需要什么礼物吗？
Oh, Susannah.You know what gift I'd really love?
你他妈给老子闭嘴 臭婆娘！
If you would just shut up!
你这个娘们儿一直发牢骚 会毁了我的扑克牌比赛兴致的
Nothing ruins a good poker game more...than a lady jabbering on and on...
太特么浪漫了
How romantic.
别来无恙啊 Custer长官
Well, General Custer!
很高兴见到你
Yes, at your service.
你好 马克吐温先生
Mr. Mark Twain.
正是在下
Word up!
先生们 请进
Gentlemen, do come in
最近还好吗 我刚才还和这位长官谈到我的新书
Yo, Zeke, big boy, I was just going off to the General here about my new book.
是《汤姆历险记》的续集
It's a sequel to Tom Sawyer.
是关于他的朋友的故事 名叫《费恩历险记》
It's about Sawyer's home slice, Huckleberry Finn.
一个白人男孩儿和他朋友的水上漂流记 人们为这个故事疯狂的！
White boy goes raftin' with a brother.People gonna lose their shit!
Custer长官 你的漂亮的金色头发长出来了
And, General Custer, I see you've let your dashing blond hair grow out.
就是 军队里面的理发师手艺太差了
Well, yes, the barber down at the regiment is just awful,
所以要么我就留长发 要么我情愿他们剥我头皮
so I had two choices, either let it grow or get scalped.
我是绝对不允许这种事情发生的
And I ain't gonna let that happen.
我们的老朋友待会儿会来吧？
Now, will our old friend from Tombstone be joining us?
他等会就来 但是今天我们有位新的参赛者 来自墨西哥的一位富人 他经营咖啡豆农场
Late as usual.But we have a new player, a wealthy Mexican coffee bean rancher.
先生们 我没迟到吧？
Am I tardy-o?
噢 吓了我一大跳 你什么时候来的
Oh.neaky little Mexican.
先生们 这位是...Don Don Diego
May I present Don Don Diego.
我们这里是来参加扑克牌比赛的 你后面的2位保镖没有必要陪同吧
We run a gentleman's game here, Mr.Diego.Your, uh, two bodyguards are completely unnecessary.
保镖？才不是 先生们 你们误会了
Bodyguards? You're mistaken, General.
这位是...Chimichanga 我的管家仆人
This is, um...Chimichanga... my loyal manservant.
愿主保佑你
God bless you.
还有....这位是Blanco Beardio
And...Blanco Beardio.
他负责今天下午比赛场上的娱乐项目演奏
He'll be providing the entertainment for this afternoon's festivities.
那先给我来一首吧
Well, drop me a beat.
先生们 每次的赌金筹码都是1万5千美元
Gentlemen, the buy-in is $15,000.
1万5千美元?
Fifteen large?
你确定“饼干”先生能付得起这个价吗？
Are you sure General Custard can swing that?
我名字叫Custer 不是Custard 后面没有字母D 我又不是甜点
It's Custer, not "Custard." There is no "D." I'm not a dessert.
嘣! 我刚刚是故意洗你娃儿脑壳的 哈哈哈
Boom, I just dropped some satire on your ass, General!
妹啊 被你算计了！
You got me!
当Ramo给我们暗号的时候 我们就开始行动
Hey! Now, when Ramon gives the signal that the time is right, that's when we move in.
你丫还记得暗号是什么吧？
You remember the signal, right?
先生们好
Gentlemen.
长官 比赛还是老地方
You know where to go, Marshal.
我天 不会吧 那人是  Wyatt Earp！！
Oh, hell, no!That's Wyatt Earp!
西部最快的枪手？
The fastest gun in the West?
先生们 我来了 我来了！
All right, all right, all right!
噢！Wyatt Earp 你终于来了！ 我等到花都谢了！
Oh, Wyatt Earp, as I live and breathe!
对不起 各位 我来晚了
Sorry I'm late, everybody.
但是现在外面有一群新团伙 到处抢钱 惹麻烦
But apparently, there's some new gang out there robbing everybody blind.
他们还给自己取了个名字 叫可笑6人帮
Oh, they call themselves the Ridiculous 6.
这个地方 你行走不到5英里 就会遇见各种亡命徒 响尾蛇 印第安人...
I swear, a man can't ride five miles in this territory without running into outlaws,rattlesnakes, Injuns and...
嘿！印第安人我来担心就够了！
Hey! Why don't you let me worry about the Injuns?
恭敬不如从命 哈哈哈
Will do, General.
最近怎样啊 吐温先生
What's shakin', Twain?
我好的不能再好了 很高兴见到你 朋友
Hey, I'm good on anything.Just like gravy, baby.Good to see you, my man.
我也是 兄弟  对了  我最近看了你的著作《王子与贫儿》
You too, man.Hey! I finally read Prince and the Pauper.
是吗 怎么样？
Oh, is that right?
没看懂
Didn't get it.
真的假的？
For reals?
我说的反话！嘣! 骗到你了！！
Satire! Boom! I got ya!
-我只是和你开玩笑而已- I'm just pulling your leg.
- 我去-Oh, man.
我的名字叫Don...Don Don Diego
Um... I am Don...Don Don Diego.
好吧 Don 我的名字叫Wyatt...Wyatt Wyatt Earp
Well, Don, I'm Wyatt...Wyatt Wyatt Earp.
搞定 现在我们开始打牌吧~~~~
Got him. Now let's play some cards!
在这个叫Wyatt Earp的人毁掉我们计划之前 我们要赶紧想办法进去
Let's get inside before this Wyatt Earp ruins our plan.
Tommy 但是门口人太多了 你怎么进去啊？
But there's no way for you to sneak past them guys, Tommy.
这里没有岩石 没有树木 没有可以做掩护的东西啊
There's no rocks, no trees, no nothing to hide behind.
当你和风是朋友的时候 你就不需要掩护
No need to hide, brother, when you are friends with the wind.
我给你说 在那边 Mexico不是墨西哥的发音
I'm telling you, down there,they don't call it "Mexico."
他们读成Mehico X发成H的音
It's "Mehico." The "X" is an "H."
那是不是德克萨斯州的读音应该是"Tehas."
'm presuming Texas is "Tehas."
就是一个风滚草 有什么大惊小怪的
Just a tumbleweed. you jumpy bastard.
我去 这是什么？
what's this?
我擦 还真特么神了
That is some mystical shit.
我想把卧室的梳妆台搬到窗口附近 但是我一个小女子没有力气做...
I wish to move the dresser in my bedroom closer to the window,but I haven't the strength to do it myself.
夫人 我真的想帮你忙 但是我必须呆在这弹钢琴
I'd love to help, ma'am, but I really should keep playing the piano.
没人会知道你离开
No one will even know you're gone.
先生们 快点下注吧
Gentlemen, cough up your buy-ins.
赶紧的 多下多得
Make it rain like Twain.
老东家 你这个酒真不赖啊 从哪里弄来的？
Sure is some good hooch there, Zeke. Where'd you find that?
噢 那瓶酒 早在20多年前我就得到了
Oh, I got that from a case about, uh, 20 years ago.
实际上 你们都知道Jawbone瀑布下面有个小木屋吧？
In fact, uh, you know that shack up by Jawbone Falls?
当时里面住了一个女的
There was a lady living there.
她是Frank Stockburn的众多情人之一
It was one of Frank Stockburn's many paramours.
但是这个女的是我这辈子见过最丑的女子
Now this was one of the ugliest ladies I've ever seen in my life.
听起来像一坨屎一样
Sounds like a real bucket of turds.
但是她确实是一名很优秀的酿酒师
But she was a very talented distiller of alcohol.
当她在给我马车装东西的时候 她的小儿子出来了
While she...While she's loading up my coach, her young boy comes out,
摇摇晃晃的呆子 不会说话 像猪一样恶心
this big shambling oaf, mute, filthy as a hog,
然后他居然开始跳起了 踢踏舞 还一边唱起了美国国歌
and he starts doing this horrible little tap dance whilst singing "The Star-Spangled Banner."
与其说是唱 不如说是低声咕噜着 像是一个原始人
Well, not singing it, really, but grunting it, like a caveman!
这个野孩子祈求我给点他点钱 我就在口袋里找了几个硬币
You know, he wants me to throw him some pennies,so I fished a coin out of my pocket
然后我就扔给了他 估计是我用力气大了点 硬币击中了他的嘴 居然把他的门牙打掉了！
and I guess I don't know my own strength.I tossed it, hit him in the mouth, and knocked his tooth out!
你丫够狠的啊！
What an asshole!
别说这些了 我还在地窖里留着一瓶这样的好酒
In any event, I still have one bottle left from that case.
等我把酒取来 来敬一敬那个可怕的女人和她丑陋的儿子！
I'll go fetch it and we can drink a toast to that awful woman and her hideous son.
我擦 如此只丑陋的女人 你根本不会想和这种女人上床
Oh, she was ugly! You wouldn't even sleep with her.
我说...Don Don Diego先生 你的筹码在哪里？
Say, Don Don Diego...where's your buy-in?
不是一个人一万5千美元吗？
I thought it was 15 grand a man.
是你！
It's you!
怎么回事？
What?
什么怎么回事？
What "what"?
你到底在惊讶什么？
What are you so surprised about?
我们在这里如此享受如此多乐趣 我感到很惊讶
Just so surprised at all the... the fun that we're having here,
有牌打 有钱使 还有好酒喝...
with the card and the money and the booze and...
其实我早上独自在家 擦古龙香水的时候 也是这幅表情
You know, I make that same face when I put my cologne on in the morning,especially when I'm home alone.
你们猜我是怎么想的？
You know what I think?
我觉得这位Don Don Diego先生根本就不是咖啡豆农场主
I think Don Don Diego isn't really a coffee bean rancher at all.
他来这里的真正目的是抢我们的钱！
And his true purpose here is to rob us.
不要逼我杀了你 Earp先生
Don't make me kill you, Mr. Earp.
把手举起来
Hands up high.
我擦 你敢对Wyatt Earp动手？
Oh, snap! You got the drop on Wyatt Earp?
他是我的兄弟  也是个狠角色哦
It's mi hermano.He's one bad hombre.
恕我冒犯 我们必须得把你们绑起来 顺便借借你们的马
No disrespect, fellas.We're gonna have to tie you up, and we'll have to borrow your horses.
喔~~我错过了什么好戏~~
Ooh, what'd I miss?
Burro 快点跑起来！！
Hurry up, Burro! Move your ass!
对头 我们来对地方了 这就是红猪岩石
Yeah, I think we found it.That is one sweet hog right there.
真是一只白白胖胖的肥猪猪
That is a sweet, majestic hog.
恩 就是 真是白胖白胖的
Yeah, that's a sweet one for sure.
看起来还好啦
It's all right.
宝宝有点困惑了 我哪里都没有看到猪猪呀
I'm confused. I don't see a hog or a pig anywhere.
伦家只看见了一个像小鸡吧的东东~
All I see is the big old rock that looks like a weenie pee-pee.
也可以 你们也可以叫小鸡鸡 小猪儿虫子
Oh, you guys call a pee-pee a "hog."
这个名字太诡异了...但是我喜欢...
That's weird. I like it, though.
问题是 我没有看见会唱歌的风车啊
Problem is, I don't see no singing windmill anywhere.
等一下...我听见了
Wait...I hear it.
对 声音就是从那边传过来的
Yeah, it's coming from over there.
啊 粑粑 我们来了 我们来了！！粑粑！！！
Ah! Daddy! Daddy!
我们得救了！ 我们得救了！！
We're saved! We're saved!
妈蛋 是我们的死对头
Oh, it's just these assholes.
你们这群傻逼怎么了
What the hell happened to you guys?
我们在抢夺了你们的钱后 逃到了Frisco
We was headed west to Frisco after we absconded with your loot.
但是我们遇到了一些真正的坏人 Cicero和他的帮派
But we ran into these real bad characters.It was Cicero something and his crazy-ass gang.
Cicero来过这里？ 然后他离开了？
Cicero was here? Then he left?
他把我们埋在土里 让我们自生自灭
He left us in the dirt for fun.
谁在敲我的头？快点滚开！！
Who does that?Sicko!
如果会唱歌的风车在这里的话 那么为什么他们一帮人会离开？
If this is where the singing windmill is,then why would they just up and leave?
或许那个教我们打球的人乱说的
Maybe that Stickie McSchnickens guy was just pulling our leg.
2个小时之前 他们往北方走了
They went north... about two hours ago.
差点忘了 Tommy可以追踪他们
Oh, yeah! Tommy can track 'em.
我们出发吧 不要在这里耗时间
Let's saddle up. We're burning daylight.
等等！！
Wait!
你们不能把我们留在这里 把我们弄出去！！
You can't just leave us here, you gotta get us out!
你们没有必要... 嘿嘿 赶紧走开
You don't need to... Hey, hey, hey!
你们的钱还在我们这人 藏在我的裤子里 我们把它还给你
We still got the money!Yeah, I hid it in my pants.We'll give it back to ya!
我们的钱已经够了 我们走！
We don't need no more. Let's go!
嘿 先别走 能不能把我胡子里面的蚂蚁赶走？
Hey! Can you at least help me pick these ants out of my beard before you head out?
求求你们了?
Please?
这样吧 如果你们答应一个条件 我们就把你们挖出来
Tell you what, we'll dig you up on one condition.
说吧 快说 我们肯定答应！
You say it, we'll do it!
你们以后不能做犯法的事情 重新做人 多多行善
That you give up your lives of crime and take this second chance to start doing good by people.
我特么情愿去死
I'd rather die!
门儿都没有！
No way!
我们刚才在开玩笑 开玩笑的！
That was a joke! That was a joke!
爸爸 我以后会变成好孩子的!
I'll be a good boy! I'll be a good boy, Daddy!
现在往哪个方向走？东边还是西边？
Now what? East or west?
今天晚些时候 有大量的人和动物经过这里
Late in the day.Lot of traffic been going through here.
我们要赶上还得花点时间
It's going to take a minute.
太好了 我们离粑粑越来越近了
Well, we must be getting mighty close.
他们对好我们父亲好点 不然要拿话来说
They'd better be treating Dad well, or they're gonna have to answer to us.
看呐 这就是我们的父亲
There he is.There's the man himself.
看呐 多么帅气的一张脸庞
Look at that handsome hombre.
这就是我们长这么帅气的原因
That's where we get our good looks.
让我看看我们的老豆
Let me see ol' Pop.
Tommy 我们父亲现在也是不是这幅长相？
Does he still
look like that, Tommy?
Tommy?
恩 长相没变
Yeah, he does.
我们今晚在这里扎营吧 就在那边
Let's set up camp tonight.
Right out there.
但是现在我们时间很宝贵啊
But we can't waste any time.
Chico...你让我好好想想吧 我需要时间思考
Chico... I can't figure it out right now.
我必须...等到日出之后...让我再想想
I gotta...Just give me till sunrise. Let me think.
亲爱的兄弟 当你们读到这封信的时候 我已经赶到父亲身边了
Dear brothers,by the time you read this, I will have caught up with Dad.
我知道我这样独自离去 你们肯定很难过
And I'm sure you're sore at me for sneaking out on you.
但是这个叫Cicero的人 不仅抓了我们父亲 而且还害死我的母亲 我会让他血债血偿
But this fellow, Cicero, who took Pa, also took my mother's life,and I mean to make him pay for that.
事情可能会一发不可收拾 我可以忍受我们做过的坏事
Things might get messy. I can live with all the bad stuff we've done,
我们一起劫持人质 一起盗窃 甚至意外杀了人
the hold-ups, the burglaries,the accidental decapitation,
但是我唯一不能忍受的就是你们之中任何一个出事
but I couldn't live with myself if something happened to one of you.
所以你们就好好地呆在这里 等我把父亲尽快地带回来
So stay put and I'll be back with Dad as soon as I can.{
如果我一直不会来的话 记住我会永远全心全意地爱你们
And if I don't come back,know that I love you boys with all my heart.
你们的兄弟 Tommy
Your brother, Tommy.
当时在银色峡谷 遇到你母亲 是我这辈子最幸运的事
Down at Silver Canyon...Meeting Betty Dunson...was the luckiest thing that ever happened to me.
遇到母亲是他一生赢得的最大比赛
Mom was his biggest score.
终于到了 我们千辛万苦来到这里 希望不会空手而归
Here we are.We'd better not have come all this way for nothing.
Frank 交出那笔钱
I want the money, Frank.
我知道你想要什么
I know what you want.
你想要的钱在这 数数
There's your money.Count it.
Tommy!
看呐 谁来了
Oh, look who showed up.
我不确定是否有人已经把你藏好的钱挖了出来 所以我又去弄了另外一笔钱 这样保险点
I didn't know if somebody dug up what you buried, Pa,so I wanted to make sure you were covered either way.
儿子 谢谢你
Thank you, son.
哟 还真是个好孩子
Well, ain't that a good boy.
是我的好儿子
That's my boy.
真是谢谢你了 Frank 但是 我得走了
Well, it's been a pleasure, Frank.But, uh...we'll be on our way.
别急着走 我们还有笔帐没算完
Not so fast.You and me got some unfinished business.
不可能 我们已经算清了
No, our business is done.
父亲 你记得我给你说过母亲是怎么死的吗?
Pa... you remember how I told you Ma died?
记得
Yeah.
有一个狗杂种开枪打死了她... 凶手的手上有个纹身
Well, the son of a bitch who shot her....had a tattoo on his hand...
和Cicero一样的纹身
just like Cicero here
什么意思 我的这个马蹄纹身？
What, you mean...my little horseshoe?
这个纹身总是能带给我好运
That's always brought me luck.
特别是我每次开枪射击人的时候
Especially when I was shooting somebody.
凶手 你的运气已经用光了
Well, killer, your luck just ran out.
如果你的手敢碰一下刀 你就会命丧黄泉
Your hand touch that knife, boy,it'll be the last thing you ever touch.
放心 我不会用这些刀的
Oh, I ain't using these knives.
不会 为了我的母亲
No.Not for my mama.
我特地给你准备了一把特别的刀
I saved a special one just for you.
你死期到了 白人的叛徒
Now you die, Injun-lover.
你敢动他一根汗毛试试？
He dies, you die.
我们有14个人 你们才6个人 寡不敌众
Fourteen of us, six of you. Doesn't seem quite fair, does it?
现在我们有12个人了
Make that twelve of us.
你他妈给我滚出来！！
Twelve of us!
为什么要逼我干这些事情
I ain't sign up for this shit.
你看到什么东西了吗？
You seeing this?
-完全不起作用 -你在干什么？
- It's not working.- What are you doing?
-看起来一点都不像风滚草 -快点回来
-Don't look like a tumbleweed at all, Herm. -Herm, come back! Come back, Herm.
好了 好了 现在每个人都冷静下来 听我说
All right, all right. Now, everybody just calm down.
这个男的杀了他的母亲 罪有应得
A man's entitled... to kill his mother's killer.
另外 你们分钱的时候 不刚好少分一个人的钱吗?
Plus... that's one less guy you've got to split the money with!
好主意 我们走！
Good thinking, Frank.Let's ride!
干得好 我的儿子 真为你感到骄傲
Good job, son. I'm really proud of you.
还一路找了这么多朋友 来帮你的忙 真聪明
And getting your friends to come all the way out here with you, brilliant.
其实...他们不仅仅是我的朋友...实际上是我的兄弟
Well, sir... they ain't just my friends, they, uh...They're my brothers.
5个？
Five?
是的 你还有5个孩子
You had fun, didn't you, sir?
好吧 那我过去给他们打声招呼吧
Well, I'm gonna introduce myself.
我想他们会很高兴的
I think they'd like that.
我叫Frank Stockburn 是你们的父亲
Frank Stockburn, your dad.
-很高兴见到你 - 也很高兴见到你
-Nice to meet you.-Nice to meet you.
- Father.
- Son.
这是我的小毛驴
This is my burro.
见到你很荣幸 burro
Proud to know you, Burro.
他很荣幸
He's proud.
你一定是Saint Louis 对吧？
You must be, uh, Saint Louis, right?
Chico.
好小子 你遗传了你母亲的好身板儿
Boy, you got your mom's muscles.
你是职业拳击手？
You a prizefighter?
恩...其实...我是一名钢琴家
No, actually, I'm a... piano player.
其实 我没事儿也喜欢弹弹钢琴
Oh, well, I'll be!You know, I've been known to tickle the ivories myself.
挺有意思的 我们应该以后一起弹奏个什么曲子
Now and then, you know.We should play together sometime.
很乐意 父亲
I'd like that, Dad.
非常乐意
I'd like that a lot.
没问题 肯定有机会的
Yeah, son, we'll do that.
你一定是Delilah的儿子
You must be Delilah's boy.
儿子 你母亲酿得一手好的威士忌
Boy, she made some fine, fine whiskey.
怀你的时候 你母亲肯定喝了不少酒吧
She must've been really hitting it hard when she was pregnant with you.
你是...?
And, uh... you are?
我叫小皮特 我是你的儿子 我灰常爱你! 粑粑!!
I'm Lil Pete. I'm your son! I love you so much, Dad!
我有3颗奶头
I have three nipples.
多多益善嘛
Yeah, well...It's always good to have a spare.
我天 你居然也有3个奶奶？！
Gall dang, you have one, too?
你喜欢玩多余的这个奶奶头吗？
Do you like to play with the extra one?
超级稀饭
Oh, you betcha.
粑粑 我想问你一个问题
Oh, Pa, I have a question for you.
宝宝都是怎么生出来的呢？
Where do babies come from?
妈妈拉屎屎的时候 宝宝就一起生出来了
Well, son, the mom just poops 'em out.
哈哈哈哈 我就知道 我就知道是这样！！
I knewed it! I knewed it, Dad!
瞧这个帅小伙儿
Well, look at this handsome devil.
我叫丹尼 终于能见到你了！
Sir, I'm Danny.It's awful nice to finally meet ya.
你能帮助我解决一个问题吗？
Could you help me with a problem?
我做了一件很蠢的事情
I did a real stupid thing
这件事情意外导致了美国总统的离世
that inadvertently led to the death of a United States President,
我一直都被这件事所困扰
and I'm feeling pretty lousy about it.
孩子 看着我的眼镜
Well, son...look in my eyes.
不好的事情时常发生
Shit happens.
说的倒是
Yeah, right.
非常感谢您的建议
Thanks. Thank you, sir.
不客气
You're welcome.
现在你们有什么打算?
So, where to now, huh?
再过几天 我就要和小狐狸结婚了
Well, sir, Smoking Fox and me are getting married in a few days,
我的养父会陪新娘走过红地毯
and Screaming Eagle's walking her down the aisle,
我希望...到时候你会站在我身边
and I was hoping...you could be there, next to me.
你意思是让我当你伴郎？
Oh, you mean your best man?
是的 父亲
Yes, sir.
Oh, Tommy...
你邀请我 我非常荣幸
You know, that's...that's quite an honor.
应该是我很荣幸
It would be my honor, sir.
但是...儿子...我得...去北边处理一些事情...
yeah. Well, uh...But unfortunately, I...I got some business up north that I gotta attend to.
我还得去还一些赌债...还得去给医生结账...
I gotta collect some gambling debts and...You know, just to pay the doctors and such.
父亲 其实你根本不用担心钱的问题
Say, Dad. You don't ever gotta worry about money ever again.
我们一共攒齐了2个5万美元！！！
We had to conjure up 50 grand twice!
当时我们一共有10万美元！！
So we ended up with 100!
10万？
A hundred?
你们手里还有5万美元？
There's another 50 grand?
Yes, sir.
就在这里 小毛驴背上背着
Right here, in the burro's saddlebag.
所以 北边的事情可以再缓缓 对吧 伴郎先生？
So that business can wait up north, can't it... best man?
既然你们这么执着 我确实要改变一下我的计划了
Well, now that you mention it, maybe I should change my plans.
什么情况 为什么那群人回来了？！
Hey! What are they doing back?
到底什么回事？
What is this?
我想是时候告诉你们真相了
I guess it's time you kids learned the truth about your dear old dad, huh?
我太臭名昭著了
I'm just too famous.
我一来到西部这些地方 就会被到处通缉
I can't walk into any town west of the Rockies without someone calling the law.
所以我想了一个妙计 一个我不需要动手 就有人帮我弄钱的好办法
So, I came up with a way we could make 50 grand without lifting a finger.
你们这群孩子居然给我弄到了双份的钱！
And you rascals brought us double!
不愧是我的亲生儿子！
Are these my kids or what?
真是他妈瞎了眼了
Son of a bitch!
如果我们2个帮派合伙 那么我们以后在西部就无敌了
If our two gangs joined forces,there's not a lawman in the West that would stand up against us.
凭什么你觉得我们会加入你？
What makes you think we'd turn to a life of crime?
因为你们天生就是干这个的
'Cause it's in your blood.
老实回答我
Answer me something.
除了偷窃 你们还做过其他什么伟大的事情没有？
Were you ever great at anything in your life besides stealing?
No. No.
你们的本性就是这样的
You apples didn't fall far from this tree.
不要否认这一点
Don't deny who you are.
如果你真的清楚我们本性的话 你就应该感到害怕了
If you knew who we really were, you'd be very scared right now.
孩子不要高估了你自己
Don't overplay your hand, son.
我还有一张王牌在手里
I'm still holding an ace.
我找到她了 告诉过你...我会找到她的...
I found her. I...I told you I'd find her.
这个小妞儿前几天闯到我们的营地里了
This little beauty stumbled into our camp a few days ago.
事实上她还是来救我的
she actually tried to rescue me.
现在你估计不想让我当你伴郎了吧 ？
I'm guessing this means you don't want me to be your best man no more, huh?
长话短说 我们速战速决
Well, I'm gonna make this real simple for you.
要么你把那个蠢货袋子里的5万块钱给我
Hand over the other 50 grand...in that stupid ass' saddlebag,
要么我就让你的未婚妻脑袋吃颗子弹
or I put a bullet in her pretty Apache head.
你做梦吧
That ain't gonna happen.
噢 不同意是吧？
Oh, it ain't?
No, sir.
为什么？
Why's that?
恩...还真是个秘密
Mmm... kind of a secret.
告诉你的父亲吧 小子
Well, you can tell your old man, can't ya?
你们手下刚才拿走的...那袋钱
You know that bag...your boy's holding?
本来是给Cicero的
It was meant for Cicero.
里面装了很特别的东西
So there's something special in there.
B计划
Plan B.
B计划？
Plan B?
B计划
Plan B.
把包给我
Give me that bag.
完蛋了
Oh, shit!
你在哪里？
Where is she?
小狐狸
Smoking Fox.
再见了 儿子
Nighty-night, son.
Danny你没事吧？
Danny, are you all right?
Danie 做得好 你救了我的命
You done good, Daniel. You saved me.
总统先生 这是我的职责
It's my duty, Mr. President.
林肯夫人你好
Mrs. Lincoln.
我打死了一个！！
I got one!
傻逼 你特么差点打死我！
Clem, you almost shot me!
这张钞票还能用吗？ 还是烧烂了？
Is this here still valid,or is it too burnt up?
让我看一下 我觉得看起来还可以用
Let me take a look here.Uh, that looks good to me. I mean, this looks good.
我操 ！！ 你根本就没有把右眼挖出来！！！
What in the hell?You didn't scoop yours out, did you?
你问的什么问题？
What was the question again?
什么？？你们是不是都没人把眼睛挖出来?
What?Did any of you really do it?
那罐子里到底装的谁的眼睛？？？！！！！
Well, then whose eyes are in that jar?
小脸孩子怪找到了一些小石头 涂了涂颜料...
Well, Babyface found some rocks, and, uh, painted them.
好看吧？...
Surprise?
嘿 Tom 想玩个游戏吗？
Hey, Tom,you wanna play a game?
来弥补我们以前失去的父子时光？
to make up for all the father-son time we missed?
来捉迷藏吧
Peek-a-boo.
嘿 快来这边
Hey, come over here!
不 来那边！
No, come over there!
你本来可以得到一切的 儿子
You could have had everything, son.
但是你非得这么正直
But you had to do the right thing.
给你一点作为父亲的建议
Let me leave you with a bit of fatherly advice.
永远不要在枪战中用刀子
Never bring a knife to a gunfight.
小狐狸 以后可能我会置你于危险之中
One day, there will be too many, my love.
但是我相信你今天不会
But not today.
这真特么神了
That was some mystical shit.
Tommy.
你一直都知道是Cicero杀了我母亲
You knew Cicero killed my mother.
怎么会 不可能 我不知道啊
No!No, I didn't know that.
到现在你还在撒谎？！！
No more lies!
好吧...我承认...我知道
Yeah, I knew. I knew.
你母亲要去告发我们
Your mother insisted on telling.
她打算把我们整个帮派都告发出去 我一直都在劝说她...
She was going to rat the whole gang out, and I tried to convince her...
Tommy 看在上帝的份上 饶了你的父亲吧
Tommy, look, I'm your father, for God's sake.
Tommy 我知道你是不会杀了你父亲的
You don't kill your father, Tommy.
他的名字是小白飞刀
His name is White Knife.
放心 我不会杀你
I ain't gonna kill you.
因为我真正的父亲是不会让我这么做的
'Cause my true father taught me otherwise.
你不能这样扔下我！
You can't leave me like this!
Tommy!
你不能把我一个人扔在这里！！
You can't leave me here alone!
亲爱的麻麻 上次给你写信以后 发生了太多的事情
Dear Mama, so much has changed since my last letter.
我都不知道从何说起了
I scarcely know where to begin.
首先 我们的父亲结果是个很坏很坏的人
First off, it turns out our daddy is a bad, bad man
他现在被关进了监狱
and he got thrown in jail.
但是没关系 Tommy的印第安养父 答应做我们所有人的父亲
But it's okay, 'cause Screaming Eagle, the Indian chief who raised Tommy said he'd be all our dads, too.
我真的很喜欢这个朴实的村庄
I really like it here in this village.
这里的兄弟姐妹们都喜欢和我们玩 对我们都很友善
Our new brothers and sisters love to have fun and have been so nice to all of us.
这些白人真得不会跳舞啊
These white guys cannot dance.
Danny以后再也不喝威士忌了
Danny don't drink whiskey no more.
Ramon 和 Herm 尝试着融入印第安人的生活当中
And Ramon and Herm are trying to learn Indian ways
噢 还有一个好消息忘了给你说
Oh, and big news..
我交了一个新的女盆友
I finally have a girlfriend
她比我的右手好使多了 嘿嘿...
and she's much prettier than a canty-loupe.
来啊 坐那里干嘛 过来一起嗨！
Come on, you two! You're missing all the fun.
最后 我要感谢你抚养了我
Anyways, Mama, thanks for raising me.
爱你的儿子 小皮特
Your loving son, Lil Pete,
并且很荣幸地成为6逗逼的成员之一
proud member of the Ridiculous 6.